我叫巴里·艾伦  是现今世上速度最快的人
My name is Barry Allen and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但当我女儿从未来时空前来帮忙
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
她改变了现在
she changed the present.
现在我们的世界比以往更加危险
And now our world is more dangerous than ever.
我是唯一一个来得及拯救世界的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
我是闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
依循我的指示我们就能打败蝉
Follow my instructions and we'll defeat Cicada.
摧毁他的匕首  救你的父亲
Destroy his dagger and save your father.
这个新的时间线挣扎着想要冲破障碍
That is a new timeline struggling to break through.
斯旺  另一个蝉出现了
Thawne, another Cicada showed up.
我也曾认为对他们隐瞒实情
I used to think that keeping secrets from people
是一种保护  但是隔着一堵墙
would protect them, but you can't really
你不可能真正了解一个人
know someone with walls between you.
艾尔伯德·斯旺  逆闪电
Eobard Thawne, the Reverse Flash.
你的搭档  你的秘密
Your partner. Your secret.
爸爸  我撒谎了  对不起
Dad, I'm sorry I lied to you!
我也是
So am I.
爸爸  求你  我想过要告诉你
Dad, please. I wanted to tell you.
爸爸  我有试着告诉你
Dad! I tried to tell you.
我撒谎了  对不起
I'm sorry I lied to you!
诺拉是我们的女儿
It's Nora, our daughter.
她骗了我们  爱瑞丝
She lied to us, Iris.
从她到这里的第一天就开始了
Since the first day she got here,
隐瞒斯旺的事
about Thawne!
她知道他对我们做了什么  对我做了什么
She knows what he did to us. To me.
对我的母亲做了什么
To my mother.
她说的话我一个字也不相信
I can't believe a word she says.
-我们还不确定  -我们很清楚
- We don't know that. - Yes, we do!
我们甚至都不知道她为什么要帮他
We don't even know why she's working with him.
现在问题的关键不是
Now the pressing question is not
诺拉为什么要帮助逆闪电
why Nora is workingwith the Reverse Flash.
也许我可以和她谈谈  了解一下此事
Maybe I can talk to her and shed some light on the matter.
我想你了解的已经够多了
I think you've shed enough light.
怎么  你在生我的气吗  我应该怎么做
Why, are you upset at me? What I should do?
我不应该告诉你们吗
I should just--I should not have told you?
你怀疑她多久了
How long has it been since you suspected her?
从我来到这开始
Since I arrived.
所以你一直在追踪这条线索
So you've been following this trail all this time
但是直到现在才告诉我们
and you didn't think to tell us about it until now?
我不知道这条线索会指向何处
I don't know where this trail leads.
-你在开玩笑呢吧  -我很认真
- Are you kidding me? - I'm not kidding you.
你不能没有证据就轻易下结论
You don't come to a conclusion without facts.
所有的证据
All the facts.
秀兰  我想  或许你得
Shirley, I think, uh, maybe you should just
给我们一点时间缓缓
give us all a minute here.
怎么了  你们生我的气
What, you're mad at me
因为我做了一个侦探大师该做的事
for doing what a master detective does.
搞清楚了你们无法弄清的事
Figure out something that you cannot.
是我给出了那些符号的译文
I give you that translation.
你们不该对我生气
Your anger is misplaced.
无论诺拉是因为什么缘故对我们隐瞒实情
Look, whatever reason Nora didn't tell us,
我都不认为她这么做是出于恶意
I don't think she did it maliciously.
即使在这儿  我也能感受到她有多难过
Guys, even from here, I can feel how upset she is.
亲爱的  你和诺拉相处
All right, babe, you've been around Nora
有好几个月了
for months.
你此前从没感觉到她有所隐瞒
You never felt that she was hiding something before.
没有  从未  从来没有过
No, never. Never.
斯旺撒谎成性  他可是这方面的大师
Well, Thawne lied. He was a master at it.
这很合理  他一定是教了诺拉
It stands to reason he must have taught Nora
一些他的独门秘笈
some of his same tricks.
也许是这样  也许不是
Maybe. Maybe not.
一定有办法弄清楚的
There's gotta be some way to figure it out.
有的
There is.
我在想这里面记录着
I'm guessing this has everything
从她到这里那天开始的一切
from the day she arrived.
或许还记录着那之前的事
Maybe before.
那就看吧
Read it.
从头开始
From the beginning.
闪 电 侠
第五季
第十八集
2049年
请往后站
Please stand back from the perimeter.
代顿实验室
对不起  抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry.
对不起  对不起  借过
Uh, excuse me. Excuse me, pardon me.
-母亲来电  -妈妈  拜托
- Incoming call from Mom. - Mom, come on.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
只是  我已经晚了
I just--I'm really late.
有一个很重要的约会  我已经晚了很多了
I'm--I'm really late for an important date.
不是恋爱约会那种
Not a date, date.
我也不是不和人约会
Not that I don't date, date. I date, date.
我只是要赶去一个会面
It's just, I have a meeting.
我再说下去只会迟到更久  抱歉
I'm making myself later. Sorry.
有人看见犯罪现场鉴证员吗
Anyone seen CSI?
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
韦斯特艾伦在哪
Where is West-Allen?
非常抱歉  柯蒂斯警探
Ah, I'm so sorry, Detective Curtis.
我不是有意要迟到的
I didn't mean to be late.
我尝试过在路边打的  但他们都没停下
I tried to hail a hover-taxi but they kept passing me by
然后我只好一路跑过来
and then I had to run all the way from--
我真的不在乎
I really don't care what
你这次又有什么借口  韦斯特艾伦
your reason is this time, West-Allen.
我只想知道这是哪种超能力者做的
I just wanna find what meta did this.
当然
Of course.
化学品运输车在驶向代顿实验室途中
Chemical transport truck on its way to Dayton Labs.
今天一大早遭遇袭击
It was attacked earlier this morning.
这样本周已经有两所实验室
But that makes two labs
还有两辆运输车遭遇了袭击
and another two transports this week.
并且和那些案件一样  没有目击证人
And like the others, no one saw anyone.
天呐  这里到处都是残留物
God, there's residue everywhere.
苯甲醇
-苯甲醇  -这就是他们偷走的东西
- Benzene Methanol. - That's what they stole.
那是用来做什么的
What's that used for?
扫描中
小到用于治疗虱病  大到用于纳米科技
Anything from nanotech to treating lice.
-氟烷  -氟烷
- Halothane. - Halothane?
氟烷
-等一下  -怎么了
- Wait a second. - What?
这辆卡车装有亲和牌4000型安保摄像头
This truck has an Affinity 4,000 security camera.
天呐  莉娅一定会羡慕死的
God, Lia's gonna be so jealous.
每当这个摄像头被干预时
Whenever the 4,000's tampered with,
它的故障保险装置就会释放一种麻醉剂
its failsafe releases a incapacitating agent.
氟烷
Halothane.
所以你是说作案者撬了锁
So you're saying whoever did this picked the lock,
弄坏了摄像头
disabled the camera,
然后偷走了或许能治虱病的药物
and stole, might be lice medicine?
在麻醉剂还没起效前就搞定了这一切
All before this incapacitating agent could do its job?
而且还没被人看见
And no one saw them.
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
极速者
A speedster?
诺拉  实验室同事  我的好朋友
Nora, labmate, friend of mine,
你没把你的极速者理论
You didn't happen to pitch your speedster theory
告诉柯蒂斯警探  对吧
to Detective Curtis, did you?
这不止是理论  莉娅  这是唯一的解释
It is not a theory, Lia. It is the only explanation.
你知道的  我基本上已经是
You know I'm equally a fan
我们的飞毛腿超级英雄的粉丝了
of our fleet-footed super friends.
说老实话  如果我能
I mean, honestly, if I could have ever
见到杰西·快客  肯定把她当我的新闺蜜
met Jesse Quick, it's like, hello, new best friend.
-不要不开心  -的确有点不开心
- No offense, um-- - Some taken.
但是在你妈妈发表那篇
Okay, but there hasn't been a speedster
关于危机事件的文章后
in Central City since that crisis piece
中城已经几十年没出现过极速者
your mom wrote about, like, decades ago.
闪电侠  闪电小子  杰伊·加里克
I mean, Flash, Kid Flash, Jay Garrick,
那个带紫色闪电突然出现的奇怪极速者
that-- that weird purple speedster that just showed up one day.
他们全都不见了
They're all gone.
所以你说的这种可能性非常低
So what you're suggesting, highly unlikely.
那我们要开始相信这种极低的可能性
Then we need to start believing in the highly unlikely.
或者你也许...
Alternatively, um, you could--
不要这么痴迷
dial back your obsessiveness.
我才没有痴迷
I'm not obsessive.
你一直没机会了解你父亲
You never got to know your dad.
所以你像他一样  做了一个鉴证员
So you became a CSI just like him,
所以你一直在调查
and it's why you keep investigating the one case
巴里·艾伦没能查出的这件案子
Barry Allen never solved.
《中城市民》蝉是谁
蝉
Cicada.
你把这称为痴迷  这只是我一个爱好
You call that obsessive. I call that a hobby.
好吧  你的典型日常
Right, your, um-- your classic everyday...
追查凶杀的爱好
murder hobby.
就像你妈妈说的
It's like your mom says.
你过头了
You're, uh-- you're excessive.
不要引用我母亲的话
Do not quote my mother.
希望中城警局能采购那种亲和牌摄像头
God, I wish CCPD would spring for one of these Affinity cameras.
兆帧  光线抓拍
I mean, trillion FPS, captures light in motion.
这是什么鬼
W-T-Shrap?
-是闪电  -毒气罐不见了
- That's lightning. - The canister's gone.
白色闪电  是极速者
White lightning. A speedster.
-也许是  -不  不是也许
- Okay, maybe. - No, not maybe.
就是闪电  我就知道
It is! I knew it!
好吧  你说得对  但是
Okay, fine, you're right. But...
但是极速者偷化学物干什么
But what is a speedster doing stealing chemicals?
艾尔伯德·斯旺  外号逆闪电
And Eobard Thawne, aka the Reverse-Flash,
逆闪电
终于被抓获收押
was finally defeated and incarcerated
并且他会在铁山监狱终生监禁
and will remain in Iron Heights Prison for the rest of his days.
反派大厅
我知道
I know.
妈妈来电
Incoming call from Mom.
逆闪电
我就知道
See? I knew it.
闪电类型
黄色
红色
蓝色
紫色
根本没有带白色闪电的极速者
There was never a speedster with white lightning.
-到你了  -谢谢
- All yours. - Thanks.
谢谢各位今天来参观闪电侠博物馆
Thank you for visiting the Flash Museum today.
极速
博物馆即将关闭
博物馆五分钟后将要闭馆
The building will be closing in five minutes.
所有游客请往出口走
All guests should make their way to the exit now.
诺拉·韦斯特艾伦  你母亲打来电话
And Nora West-Allen, your mother called.
萨维塔
请为了你我都好
Please, for your sake and mine,
回她电话吧
call her back.
反派大厅
太丢人了
So embarrassing.
妈  你为什么打给迈尔斯先生
Mom, why are you calling Mr. Myles?
我打去你实验室  你不接电话
I tried you at your lab. You weren't answering.
我给你留言三次
I left three messages.
你一直不回
You never returned any of them.
我还能怎么办
What else was I supposed to do?
等我回你电话不行吗
Wait for me to call you back?
你为什么不开全息视频
Why isn't your holo on?
在闪电侠博物馆里用不了
Uh, it doesn't work in the Flash Museum.
我实在是无法理解
For the life of me,
你对博物馆这么着迷
I've never understood your obsession with that place.
你去那里做什么  你一个人去的吗
What are you even doing there? Are you there alone?
别问了  妈  我是来查案的
It's fine, Mom. I'm researching a case.
-什么案子  -我不能讨论的案子
- What kind of case? - One that I can't talk about.
我是你妈妈  诺拉
I'm your mother, Nora.
而我在中城警局工作
And I'm an employee of CCPD
我不能讨论正在调查的案子
who can't talk about open cases.
妈  这个我得和你说多少次
Mom, how many times do I have to tell you this?
你的丈夫以前也是鉴证员
You were married to a CSI.
是的
Yes, I was.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你打来找我有什么事
What were you calling about?
我以为我女儿可能想知道
I thought my daughter might want to know
我在海滨城的近况
how I'm doing in Coast City.
我的报道就快写完了
I almost finished my story.
过几天我就回家了
I should be home in a few days.
好极了
Great.
妈  我要挂了  要去工作
Uh, Mom, I gotta go. It's work.
-爱你  -爱你
- Love you. - Love you.
来欧林实验室见我
Hey, meet me at Ollins Laboratory.
我把失窃的化学物清单发给了我以前的老师
I sent the list of stolen chemicals to an old teacher of mine
他好像查到了什么
and I think he found something.
欧林实验室
谢谢你的帮忙  邦维博士
Appreciate the help, Dr. Bonwit,
-尤其是这么晚了  -不用谢
- especially at this hour. - Not a problem.
反正欧林也一直让我加班
Ollins never lets me leave this place anyway.
莉娅和我说你也许知道这些化学物
So Lia was telling me you might know
是如何一起使用的
how these chemicals can be used together.
一半一半吧
Yes and no.
化学结构组合
所需  交互  读取
欧林实验室
我花了一点时间才看出来
Took me a bit to see it,
但只有他们被组合在同一种结构上
but the only way they seem to work together is
这些化学物才能一起产生效果
if they're built on a structure.
分子组合
比如细胞外基质
Like an extracellular matrix.
但是细胞外基质有成千上万种
But there are thousands of extracellular matrices.
所以在我们知道所有的化学物之前
So until we know all the chemicals,
我们无法知道最终结果
we won't know the end results.
抱歉我只能帮你们这么多
Sorry I can't help more.
没事  谢谢你  邦维博士
That's okay. Thanks, Dr. Bonwit.
现在怎么做
Now what?
我们不能等着下一个实验室遇袭
We can't just wait for another lab to get hit.
我的天
Holy shrap!
邦维博士
Dr. Bonwit!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
没错  我的确是神
Yes, I am a god.
速度之神
The god of speed.
快走  快走
Go, go, go, go, go!
诺拉
Nora!
快来人  快来人啊
Somebody help, please! Someone help!
诺拉
Nora?
我就知道老歌能唤醒你
Oh, I knew an oldie would wake you up.
别紧张  我们在医院
Okay, don't freak. Uh, we're in a hospital.
我手上被灼伤了  但你比我严重多了
Me for this burn and you for a whole lot more.
-邦维博士呢  -在重症室
- Dr. Bonwit? - Uh, ICU.
但是他会好起来的
But he's gonna pull through.
可那个极速者带着大量的二硫化碳逃走了
Um, but the speedster did get away with a crazy amount of carbon disulfide.
现在别担心那个了
Don't worry about that right now.
你感觉如何
How are you feeling?
实际上  我感觉挺好的
I--I feel fine, actually.
我的手指有些发麻  但除了这个
My fingers are a little tingly but other than that,
我感觉很好  很奇怪吧
I--I feel really good. It's weird, right?
你没事太好了
I'm just so glad you're okay.
你的医生说你被五十亿焦耳的
Your doctor said you got hit with five billion joules
电流击中  所以我就...
of electricity. Which means, um, I, uh--
我通知了你的母亲  她...
I, uh, kind of called your mom. Um, and she, uh--
她惊慌得很失常  但我也没办法
She freaked more than normal. Um, I had to.
-你差点死了  -莉亚  她在这里吗
- You could have died. - Lia, is she here?
她正从海滨城赶过来
She's on her way from Coast City.
她肯定急炸了
Uh, and she is wearing her aggro pants.
我是说  她给我打了47多次电话
I mean, she has called me, like, 47 times.
你应该无视她
You should have ignored her.
我就是不想让她担心
Just, I don't want her to worry.
我无视了
I did.
所以她才不知道这个
Uh, which is why she doesn't know about this.
医护人员说你来的时候
The paramedics said that you went into cardiac arrest
心搏停止了  所以他们用除颤器
when you got here and so they had to use the defib nodes
复苏你的心脏  当他们进行的时候
to restart your heart, and when they did,
他们发现了这个
they found this.
这埋在你右肩膀的伤疤下面
It was buried underneath the scar under your right shoulder.
这是什么
What is it?
他们说是你撞到的金属架
They say it's a metal scrap from the shelf
上边的碎屑  但我不确定
you got thrown into, but I don't know.
这个看起来挺老旧  而且烧焦了
It looks kind of old and--and pretty fried.
好吧  暂停  现在我们知道你没事了
Okay, wait, but now that we both know you're okay,
我们能不能讨论下你被
can we please talk about the fact that you got struck
极速者闪电击中这件事
by lightning from a speedster?
太酷炫了吧
So schway, right?
唯一的问题就是没人会相信我们
The only thing is no one's gonna believe us.
咱俩都看到了  他们不能不信
We both saw it. They're gonna have to.
保持冷静
Stay calm.
有意外发生  系统正在检查
There has been an incident. System check in progress.
怎么回事
What the hell?
接住
Catch this.
我没事
I'm okay!
你确定吗
You sure?
当然  老兄  我是极速者了
Yeah, dude. I'm a speedster.
我的神经都在抽搐  神经突触一定在发狂
All of my nerves are tingling and my synapses must be going crazy
因为我的反应时间快得爆表了
because my reaction times are way off the charts.
我要怎么面对我妈妈
What am I gonna do about my mom?
每次只要有人提到超能力者她都会发疯
She freaks out any time someone even says the word meta.
好吧  这可以理解
Okay, well, that's understandable.
我是说  她普通人丈夫因为超能力者而死
I mean, her non-meta husband died because of metas.
对  但是报道闪电侠  最伟大的超能力者
Yeah, but writing about the Flash--the meta-human--
-成就了她的事业  -所以我们不能告诉她
- made her career. - So we can't tell her?
不行  我们不能告诉任何人
No, we can't tell anybody.
至少在我们找出我如何获得能力之前不行
Not until we figure out how I got these powers.
我觉得这发生在我碰到
And I don't think it's a coincidence that this happened
那个速度之神家伙之后不是个巧合
after my little run-in with the god of speed guy.
你说的是神速用他的闪电击中了你
You mean when Godspeed hit you with his lightning.
根据闪电侠博物馆里说的
Which, according to the Flash Museum,
这获得能力的情景完全和
is exactly what happened to--
闪电侠一样
The Flash.
抢劫进行中
10-90 in progress.
银行抢劫
Bank heist.
不行不行  你不能这么做
No, no. You can't do that.
这主意不好
That is a bad idea.
就如同自己剪刘海一样不好
That is like cut your own bangs bad.
我就是小小的去一下
I'm just gonna do a little run-by.
你是现场调查员  不是超级英雄
You are a CSI, not a superhero.
我们的工作和警察没区别
Our jobs are the same as the cops.
我们抓坏人
We get the bad guys.
好吧  去抓他们吧  闪电女侠
All right. Go get 'em, Flash Woman.
闪电女士
Lady Flash.
性感闪电
Hot Flash.
这个不行
Not that one.
好吧  咱们等下再讨论名字
Okay, we're gonna workshop that later.
在那之前  我要守护中城
Until then, I have to guard Central City.
停下  不然我就开枪了
Stop or I'll fire!
把你的手放在我能看到的地方
Keep your hands where I can see them!
真对不起  你还好吗
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
别动
Freeze!
搞什么呢
What in the world?
错误与字节  你们被捕了
Bug and Byte, you're under arrest!
-快快快  -抓住他们
- Go, go, go! - Take them down!
你弄砸了夹击行动和半支小队
You fried your gauntlet and half the fleet.
只是三辆警车而已
It was only three cruisers.
现在弗伊队长怒火冲天
Now Captain Frye's gonna be on his warpath
每个人的日子都不好过了
which is gonna make everybody's life miserable.
对不起  诺拉
I'm sorry, Nora.
我知道今天不太顺利
I know today didn't exactly go so great.
两个劫匪因为我跑掉了
Both robbers got away because of me.
别那么为难自己了
Cut yourself a slice of slack pie.
这是你的第一天  又没人受伤
It was your first day. No one got hurt.
再说了  他们发现错误与字节躲在
And plus they found Bug and Byte hunched over
走私者营地  十分钟后就抓到了
with runner's cramps, like, ten minutes later.
但我还是感觉很糟
But I still feel so bad.
你看这事的方向错了
You're looking at this all wrong.
今天不是诺拉的大失败
Today was not Nora's big failure.
今天是闪电女神的大亮相
Today was the Femme-Flash's big debut.
给超级英雄命名可不简单
Naming superheroes is not easy.
莉娅  你是一个糟糕极速者
Lia, you are the best friend a shrappy speedster
能渴求的最好朋友
could ever ask for.
但我觉得中城警局没有能力
But I think we both know that CCPD isn't equipped
阻止这家伙
to stop this guy.
我们能在这家伙伤害到别人之前
The only way we're gonna catch him before
抓住他的唯一办法就是我开始
anyone else gets hurt is if I start thinking
用邪恶极速者的方式思考
like a villainous speedster.
那你要怎么做到这个呢
And how are you gonna do that?
我要去见一个
I'm gonna go see one.
逆闪电啊
Reverse-Flash, huh?
警官  你是这15年来第二位
Well, officer, you're, like, the second person in 15 years
来探视这个疯子的
who's come to visit this psychopath.
连给他打电话的人都没有
Not even a call.
你确定要独自见他吗
Are you sure you want to interview him by yourself?
我之前也独自面对过罪犯
I've been alone with criminals before.
你有五分钟
You have five minutes.
艾尔伯德·斯旺
Eobard Thawne?
我叫诺拉·韦斯特艾伦  犯罪现场调查员
My name is Nora West-Allen, and I'm a CSI tech
中城警局的
with the CCPD.
如果可以  我想要问你几个问题
I wanted to ask you a few questions, if I could.
靠近点
Come closer.
诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
Nora West-Allen.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
这间牢房的抑制能力
The dampening capabilities of this cell can negate
可以控制住一千个超能力者
the powers of 1,000 meta-humans.
玻璃  墙壁  屋顶  地板
The glass, the walls, the ceiling, the floors
都被连接上了触发器
are all connected to a power energizer that will zap
一旦抑制器失效  就会立刻输送
this place with 400 kilojoules instantly
40万焦耳电流进入房间中
should the dampeners fail.
让牢房无法被穿透
Making the cell phase-proof.
我伤害不了你  诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
I couldn't hurt you, Nora West-Allen.
就算我想也没用
Even if I wanted to.
你要问什么
What are your questions?
你是怎么落到如此地步
How did you end up in here?
中城警局里没人能
Was there nobody at CCPD that could answer
回答你这个问题吗
that question for you?
所有关于逆闪电的档案
All the files pertaining to the Reverse-Flash
都上了网络锁
have been cyber locked.
闪电侠博物馆里关于你的资料寥寥无几
And there's almost nothing about you in the Flash Museum.
除了有记录你被判入狱之时
Except for the date of your imprisonment.
真的吗
Really?
闪电侠博物馆里就只有这些
That's all there is in the Flash Museum?
那可真有趣
That's interesting.
你能告诉我  你是怎么被打败的吗
Will you tell me how you were defeated?
你为什么想知道
Why do you want to know that?
这将对我们的调查有帮助
It'll help us with an investigation.
你应该练习好如何撒谎
You need to work on your lying.
诺拉
Nora.
你的鞋是新的
Your shoes are new.
但鞋底却已经磨破
But your soles are worn.
你的袖子有烧焦的痕迹
You have singe marks on your sleeves
裤腿上也是
and singe marks on your pant legs,
但最重要的一点是
but most of all,
你的脸颊因经历吹风伤后而通红
your cheeks are flushed with windburn.
我太了解这种吹风伤了
Oh, I know that windburn.
我仍然能感觉到它
I can still feel it.
你是极速者
You're a speedster.
时间到了
Time's up.
拜托  我需要你的帮助
Please, I need your help.
出来吧  该走了
Come on. Let's go.
忏悔的时间到了  教授
Time to repent, professor.
我的超能力被斯旺发现了
Thawne figured out I had powers,
但他不肯告诉我任何关于他们的事情
but he wouldn't tell me anything about them.
怎么了
What?
别告诉我你没事
And don't tell me it's nothing
因为你整张脸都在告诉我有事
'cause your whole face says it's something.
你还记得他们在你肩膀里发现的
You know this metal fragment they found
-金属碎片吗  -是的
- underneath your shoulder? - Yeah.
有些疑问一直困扰着我
Well, something about it was bugging me,
所以我做了些调查
so I did some digging.
原来这不是倒在你身上的架子的碎片
It turns out it's not from that shelf you got thrown into.
这是  这是科技产品
It's, uh--It's tech.
是一枚尖端科研实验室在25年前制造的芯片
A chip made by S.T.A.R. Labs 25 years ago.
类似那种  找迷路的动物的芯片吗
Like a chip you would use to find a lost animal?
-这是用来抑制你的超能力的  -什么
- It's to dampen your speed. - What?
你不是因为被神速的闪电击中
You didn't get your powers when Godspeed hit you
而获得超能力的
with his lightning.
似乎是与生俱来的
It looks like you always had them.
我  我一直都有超能力
I--I've always had powers?
为什么  谁会在我体内植入超能力抑制芯片
Why do--Who would put a power dampening chip inside of--
吉特咖啡店
你妈妈欺骗了你一辈子
Your mom lied to you your whole life.
这不仅仅是生气那么简单
I mean, that's next-level aggro.
她怎么能够向我隐瞒我这种事情
How could she keep something like that from me?
她会有什么还瞒着我
I mean, what else has she lied to me about?
我觉得你得向她问清楚
I think you're gonna have to ask her.
光是想想就把我气得怒火中烧
Oh, just the idea of that makes my blood boil.
这应该是喝了玛奇朵的原因
That could be the macchiato.
我可能加了有三份浓缩咖啡
It's possible I might have made that a triple.
至少我还有可以信赖的人
At least I have one person in my life I can still trust.
-三份  -已经加了的
- A triple. - That's been established.
不不不  我不是说咖啡  是的  是咖啡
No, no, no, not the coffee. I mean, yes, the coffee.
神速偷的化学药品
But the chemicals that Godspeed stole.
苯甲醇的属性极不稳定
Benzene Methanol is unstable,
如果再加上他从欧林实验室偷的二硫化碳
and if you add the Carbon Disulfide that he stole from Ollins lab--
大爆炸
Kablooey.
我记得在九年级的分析化学课上学过
I remember that from 9th grade Analytical Chem.
组合这些化学物质的唯一方法是
And the only way to combine all those chemicals together
加入具有粘合性的物质
is if you add some kind of binding property.
对  你需要加一氧化态的物质
Right, you'd need a plus-one oxidation state,
比如  二氟化二氧
like a--a Dioxygen Difluoride.
没错  中城唯一可以储藏
Yes, and somewhere that's able to store that
这种化学药品的地方是
and the only place in Central City that can
斯塔格工业
is Stagg Industries.
我不敢相信自己第一次来斯塔格工业
I cannot believe my first time at Stagg Industries
竟是个窃贼
is as a burglar.
还是说我们是义警
Or are we vigilantes?
莉娅  我找到了
Lia, I found it.
除非你的超级速度带来了超级二头肌
Unless your super speed came with super biceps,
不然我们肯定没法把这玩意弄出去
we are not getting this out of here.
那是我的
That's mine.
好吧  你尝试打开盖子
Uh, okay. Try and get this open.
它可以瞬间蒸发
It'll evaporate in seconds.
你想要的话  先过我这关吧
If you want it, you're gonna have to come through me to get it.
你和我一样是极速者
Ah, you're a speedster like me.
所以你也需要它
So you need it too.
抱歉
Sorry.
不要
No!
莉娅  莉娅
Lia! Lia!
莉娅
Lia!
她认为自己在这世上唯一可以信赖的人
The one person in the world she thought she could trust
死在了她的怀里
died in her arms.
诺拉肯定感觉十分孤单
Nora must have felt completely alone.
-但她并不孤单  -是  她是的
- But she wasn't. - Yes, she was.
因为我没有对她坦诚相待
Because I wasn't honest with her.
爱瑞丝
Iris--
我对她做了那种事后  她还给我第二次机会
After all I did, she gave me a second chance.
这是我们至少能为她做的
It's the least we can do for her.
妈妈
Mom?
别让我后悔
Don't make me regret this.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我给女儿一个机会来为自己辩解
I'm giving our daughter the chance to explain this for herself.
诺拉
Nora.
我听说了莉娅的事
I heard about... Lia.
宝贝  我很遗憾
Honey, I'm so sorry.
我理解你失去爱的人的感受
I know how it is to lose someone you love.
如果你现在不想谈这事
If you don't wanna talk about it right now,
没关系
that's okay.
可能只是你不愿意和我聊而已
Or maybe you just don't wanna talk about it with me.
诺拉  我只是想知道你还好吗
Nora, can I just make sure that you're okay?
诺拉  我刚刚去了医院  他们说你已经走了
Nora, I went to the hospital and they said that you left.
我想被闪电击中也并没有那么痛
I guess lightning doesn't hurt as much
毕竟它在我的血液里流淌
when you already have it coursing through your veins.
看着眼熟吗
Does this look familiar?
现在呢
How about now?
-诺拉...  -莉娅在她去世之前发现的
- Nora-- - Lia found it before she died.
你把它植入我的体内  妈妈
You put this inside of me, Mom.
为了抑制我的超能力
To dampen my powers?
你欺骗了我一辈子
You lied to me my whole life.
我知道
I know.
还有谁知道
Who else knows?
还有谁
Who else?
全部人
Everyone.
所有人
Everybody?
所有我爱的人都在隐瞒我吗
Everyone that I love has been keeping this from me?
-为什么  -是我要求他们的
- Why? - Because I told them to.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
诺拉  我在试着保护你
Nora, I was trying to protect you.
-保护什么  -不要受到这座城市的伤害
- From what? - From this city.
避免受到超能力者  和你自己的伤害
From--from meta-humans. From--from yourself.
-诺拉  你不明白  -是  我是不明白
- Nora, you don't understand. - No, I don't understand.
我怎么得到自己的能力的
How did I get my powers?
你为什么讨厌极速者
What do you have against speedsters?
诺拉  我已经失去这么多了
Nora, I have already lost so much.
我不能再冒险失去你
I can't risk losing you too.
你还是失去了我
Well, you just did.
我也会想念莉娅的
I'm gonna miss Lia too.
韦斯特艾伦  我们都知道你们关系好
West-Allen, we all know how close you two were.
如果你需要休息一段时间  我相信弗伊队长...
If you need some time off, I'm sure Captain Frye--
我们得抓住行凶的人
We need to get the guy who did this.
不论什么代价
Whatever it takes.
我们检测了罪案现场的证据
We ran the evidence from the crime scene.
证明莉娅的出伤口有陌生DNA
Turns out there was foreign DNA in Lia's exit wound.
我们已经以此找出了凶手
But we've used it to positively ID this guy.
奥古斯特·哈特  生物黑客
August Hart. Bio-hacker.
水星实验室实习生  之后读研究生
Mercury Labs intern, and then grad school.
都是你的了
All yours.
这上说他因为在昏迷病人身上
Says he was kicked out for testing
实验超光速粒子兴奋剂而被开除
tachyon stimulants on coma patients.
到底什么是超光速粒子
What the hell's a tachyon?
一种比光速还快的粒子
A particle that moves faster than light.
逮捕证已经在路上了
Well, an arrest warrant's on its way now.
我保证这个人会得到应有的惩罚
I promise you this guy's gonna get what he deserves.
是  他会的
Yes, he will.
你知不知道并不是所有反派都有超能力
Did you know not all villains had meta-human powers?
有些...
Some u--
-你们一定要拍下这个  -大家快走
- Make sure you get this. - Everybody move!
神速的闪电
Godspeed's lightning...
变成了蓝色  像极速一样
It turned blue, just like Zoom's.
等等
Hey, wait a sec.
中城时报
闪电侠阻止邪恶女极速者
逆闪电
虽然她的身体分解了
Although her body disintegrated,
当局在水星实验室找到了证据
authorities uncovered evidence at Mercury Labs
违法速度增强剂  终极速度-9
of the illegal speed-enhancement drug, velocity-9.
这种挥发性的刺激物给了弹道惊人的速度
This volatile stimulant gave Trajectory incredible speed,
但付出了致命的代价
but at a deadly price.
就是这个
That's it.
苯甲醇  二硫化碳
Benzene Methanol, Carbon Disulfide,
二氟化二氧
Dioxygen Difluoride.
终极速度-9的细胞外基质的基础
The base for the extracellular matrix for Velocity-9.
只是他想做一个永久性的
Only he's trying to make one that will last forever.
我怎么阻止一个极速者
How do I stop a speedster?
-你不能  -独自去不行
- You can't. - Not alone.
但是和你  我可以
But with you, I can.
不行
No.
那个基座可以接来电
That plinth, it takes incoming calls
据我所知  你还剩几个
and from what I hear, you have a few left.
你可以通过通讯告诉我
You could walk me through it via comms.
不行
No.
他偷了足够的化学药品
He has stolen enough chemicals to make
制作复制速度能力的细胞外基质
an extracellular matrix that replicates speed powers.
我要你离开
I told you to leave.
唯一能阻止他永久成为
The only thing that is stopping him from
极速者的就是稳定剂
becoming a speedster permanently is a stabilizing agent.
一旦他拿到手  他将势不可挡
Once he gets that, he will be unstoppable.
我要你离开  警卫
I told you to leave! Guard!
拜托
Please.
他在我面前杀了我最好的朋友
He killed my best friend in front of me.
她因为他死了  你是唯一能够
She's gone because of him, and you are the only person
阻止他的人
that can stop it.
搞什么  你必须马上离开
What the hell? You need to leave now.
诺拉
Nora.
翠西·布兰德大楼
我在加州大学创新实验室  你在吗
Okay, I'm at the innovation lab at CCU. Are you there?
Q实验室
哥德尔半径转换器使用中
我在
Yes, I'm here.
好  你确定这会使扫描电路短路吗
Okay, are you sure this is gonna short out the scanner circuits?
我确定
Yes, I'm sure.
双手一起振动  制造电击
Vibrate your hands together. Build an electric shock.
好
Okay.
酷炫
Schway.
真的有用
It worked.
现在找最亮的房间
Now look for the brightest room.
转换器需要恒定的荧光灯
The converter needs constant fluorescent light.
现在定位生物识别转换器
Now locate the biometric converter.
是一个肾脏形状的物体
It will be a kidney-shaped object.
我想我找到了
I think I found it.
神速现在没有办法让他的终极速度-9稳定下来了
No way for Godspeed to stabilize his Velocity-9 now.
不吸取教训  是吗
You don't learn, do you?
那是我的
That's mine.
来拿
Come and get it.
真的有用
It worked!
不  他还有终极速度-9
No. He's got more V-9.
诺拉  你现在得离开那里
Nora, you need to get out of there now.
立刻
Right now!
我甩不掉他
I can't lose him!
斯旺
Thawne!
你听到了吗  我说我甩不掉他
Did you hear me? I said I can't lose him!
好吧  诺拉  你看到你周围
All right, Nora, do you see any walls
有墙吗  最好是混凝土的
near where you are, preferably concrete?
为什么
Why?
因为我想让你冲过去
Because I want you to run into one.
或者说  穿进去
Or rather, through one.
我不能穿过混凝土墙
I can't run through a concrete wall!
你可以
Yes, you can.
如果你以空气的相同频率振动
If you vibrate at the natural frequency of air,
你的身体  细胞所处的状态
your body--your cells will be in such a state
将能够使你穿墙而过
that they will phase right through that wall.
我做不到
I can't do this!
诺拉  听我说
Nora, listen to me.
听我的声音
Listen to my voice.
呼吸
Breathe.
感受你脸上的风
Feel the wind on your face.
脚下的地
The ground beneath your feet.
还有闪电
And the lightning.
它的电流流过你的血管
Its electricity surging through your veins.
从头顶到神经末梢
To your nerve endings from the crown of your head
再到脚趾  就像触电一样
to the tips of your toes like an electric shock
你永远不会想要结束
you never want to end.
你现在是更伟大力量的一部分
You're part of something greater now, Nora.
你是神速力的一部分  它的力量
You are part of the Speed Force and its power,
为你所用  就是现在
it's power is yours to use. Now do it.
我做不到
I can't.
I can't do it.
那再见了  小极速者
Then good-bye, Little Runner.
不  我很抱歉
No, no. Uh, I'm sorry.
我相信你  现在怎么办
I trust you. Uh, what now?
诺拉  你不能一直跑下去
Nora, you can't run forever.
你必须阻止他
You're gonna have to stop him.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you see around you.
我在五号公路和公园交口
I'm on 5th and Park.
我看到蔡氏企业  点点币银行
I see Choi Enterprises, Peercoin Bank,
还有中城公民媒体
and CC Citizen Media.
媒体  有卫星
Media, the satellites.
诺拉  我们要利用卫星的电磁辐射
Nora, we're gonna use the satellites' electromagnetic radiation
来击破终极速度-9的基因链
to break the V-9 bonds.
让神速体内充满抗内啡肽
Flood Godspeed with anti-endorphins.
马上中和终极速度-9
Neutralizing the V-9 instantly.
没错  但有个问题
Exactly, but here's the thing.
那些卫星每个小时重新校准一次
Those satellites recalibrate on the hour
同时会发射非常短的微波能量
emitting very short bursts of microwave energy.
在爆发前你只有几秒时间
You're only gonna have a few seconds to get Godspeed
把神速引到其中  你明白吗
in front of those bursts. Do you understand?
所以我只需要他跟着我进楼
So I just need him to follow me into the building.
不是进楼  是楼顶
Not into the building. Up the building.
好吧  我能做到
Uh, okay. I can do that.
我要跑多快才能跑上楼
Um, how fast do I have to go to run up a building?
能跑多快跑多快
As fast as you can.
-他来了  -跑吧  诺拉
- Here he comes. - Then run, Nora.
跑
Run.
等着  诺拉  等着
Wait for it, Nora. Wait.
就是现在
And now!
诺拉  诺拉
Nora. Nora!
我们成功了  成功了
We did it! We did it.
是的  我们成功了
Yes, we did.
我们再也不用担心神速了
Well, we don't have to worry about Godspeed anymore.
奥古斯特·哈特已被中城警局拘留了
August Hart is in the custody of CCPD.
漂亮  小极速者
Bravo, Little Runner.
我还有很多东西要学
I still have a lot to learn, you know.
-你可以教我  -我不能教你  诺拉
- You could train me. - I can't train you, Nora.
时间不够了
There's just not enough time.
你在说什么
What--what are you talking about?
-你在...  -诺拉
- You're-- - Nora.
我在地球上的时间不多了
My time on this earth is coming to an end.
我还有许多想问你的事
There's so much I wanted to ask you.
还有许多我不知道的东西
So much that I still don't know.
还有许多我妈妈骗我的东西
So much that my mom has lied to me about.
你不明白
You have no idea.
你知道什么
What do you know?
斯旺  拜托  你或许是我生命中剩下的
Thawne, please, you may be the only person left
唯一不会对我撒谎的人
in my life who won't lie to me.
诺拉
Nora,
你对闪电侠了解多少
how much do you really know about the Flash?
五  六  七
Five, six, seven.
我的天
Holy shrap.
晚上好  诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
Good evening, Nora West-Allen.
你好
Hi.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
当然  诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
Of course. Nora West-Allen.
你是爱瑞丝·韦斯特和巴里·艾伦
Daughter of Iris West and Barry Allen,
同时也被称为闪电侠之人的女儿
also known as the Flash.
你刚刚...
S--Did you--
你刚刚说我的爸爸  巴里·艾伦
Did you just say my father, Barry Allen,
是闪电侠吗
was the Flash?
你想让我播放你的视频消息吗
Would you like me to play your video message,
诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
Nora West-Allen?
给我的消息吗
My--My message?
是的  来自你的爸爸  巴里·艾伦
Yes, from your father, Barry Allen.
好吧
Uh, y--yes.
诺拉
Nora,
我没多少时间了
I don't have much time.
如果你正在看这个  就说明你和我一样
If you're watching this, it means you're like me.
你有超能力
You have powers.
也意味着我没有帮助你了解如何使用它
It also means I wasn't there to help you learn how to use them.
我将会错过你人生中很多事
I wasn't there for a lot of things.
但记住  亲爱的诺拉
Remember, my sweet Nora,
永远记住  我爱你
always remember, I love you.
我一直爱你
I always will.
我只是想见你  爸爸
I just wanted to see you, Dad.
斯旺
Thawne...
教会了我方法
showed me how.
那蝉呢
And Cicada?
我们俩无法解决的唯一案子
The one case we both couldn't solve.
是我提议来到这里解决的
It was my idea to come here and make it right.
好吧
Okay.
我能单独和诺拉聊聊吗
Can I have a minute alone with Nora?
当然可以
Of course.
你回去找斯旺多少次了
How many times did you go back to Thawne?
多少次
How many times?
在大悟之道那天晚上之后
After the night of the Enlightenment.
五次  也许是六次
Five, uh, maybe six.
你知道是他杀了我母亲你还去吗
Even knowing he killed my mother?
-爸爸  -我理解
- Dad-- - I understand...
回来见我
coming back to meet me...
和我的团队
and the team.
我真的理解
I do.
我甚至理解去见斯旺
I even understand going to Thawne...
去学习怎么做  但是...
to learn how to do it, but...
你却不断回去
you kept going back.
在知道他干了什么之后还回去
Even after you knew what he did.
即使在他不再是你唯一的选择之后
Even after he wasn't your only option anymore.
最糟糕的是  你每次都对我们撒谎
And the worst part is, you lied to us every time.
爸爸  我...
D-Dad, I--
我不相信你  诺拉
I don't trust you, Nora.
我不能让一个我不相信的人
I can't have anybody here with us
在这里和我们一起共事
that I don't trust anymore.
你在说什么
W-what are you saying?
你是时候回家了
It's time for you to go home.
爸爸  拜托别这么做
Dad, please don't do this!
我保证我不会再和斯旺见面了
I promise I will never see Thawne again!
爸爸  别这么做
Dad, don't do this!
诺拉  如果你再试图回到过去
Nora, if you try to run back in time again,
我会在神速力里感受到
I will feel it in the Speed Force.
我会知道的
I'll know.
再见  诺拉
Good-bye, Nora.
所以是她终于坦白了
So she finally came clean.
还是你自己想明白的
Or did you figure it out all by yourself?
一个还不够吗
One wasn't enough?
你还要从我身边夺走我女儿吗
You had to try to take my daughter from me too?
我的女儿
My daughter!
我就知道你会有这种反应
I knew you'd react like this.
你总是这么情绪化
You're always so emotional,
所以我才让她瞒着你
which is why I had her keep all of this from you.
你不能责怪小极速者  巴里
You can't blame the Little Runner, Barry.
她只是想和她爸爸度过一点时光
She just wanted to spend some time with her dad.
不要因此而责备她
Don't hold that against her.
把这个看作是一个死刑犯的最后需求
Consider it a condemned man's last request.
你一直以为你比我们聪明得多  斯旺
You always thought you were so much smarter than us, Thawne.
但你输了
But you lost.
现在你终于要得到报应了
And now you're finally gonna get what you deserve.